{
    "subject": "resource/Marcel_van_Eeden",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1965-11-22",
    "human_readable": "Marcel van Eeden was born on November 22, 1965.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8923072218894958,
            "question": "When was Marcel van Eeden born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8826737403869629,
            "question": "Who was born on November 22, 1965?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7877671718597412,
            "question": "What is Marcel van Eeden's date of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7872909307479858,
            "question": "What is Marcel van Eeden's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7512575387954712,
            "question": "Who was born in November of 1965?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7429794669151306,
            "question": "To what date is Marcel van Eeden's birth attributed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7159090638160706,
            "question": "On what day of the month was Marcel van Eeden born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6515166759490967,
            "question": "What day of the week was Marcel van Eeden born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5498985648155212,
            "question": "November 22nd marks the birth of whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49165064096450806,
            "question": "In what year did Marcel van Eeden come into the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marcel van Eeden was born on November 22, 1965.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2118_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=November 22nd marks the birth of whom?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2118_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What day of the week was Marcel van Eeden born on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2118_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On what day of the month was Marcel van Eeden born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2118_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2118_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2118_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2118_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2118_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2118_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2118_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2118_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2118_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2118_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2118_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all documents mention Marcel van Eeden's birthdate as November 22, 1965."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information across the documents consistently states that Marcel van Eeden was born on November 22, 1965."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The provided context states that Marcel van Eeden was born on November 22, 1965, but later mentions that he started his drawing project in 1993 depicting events that occurred before his birth. This implies that the date of his birth should be prior to November 22, 1965, which contradicts the initial claim.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources state that van Eeden's artistic practice centers around depicting events and images that predate his birth on November 22, 1965. This suggests a deliberate choice to focus on the past, making it unlikely he would base his work on events after his own birth.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "All the other sources confirm Marcel van Eeden's birthdate as 1965, with some specifying November 22.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "All provided context information consistently states that Marcel van Eeden was born on November 22, 1965. There is no information suggesting any discrepancy in his birth date across the given contexts. The reasoning behind deeming it wrong would stem from an external source or piece of information not included here, which contradicts this universally stated date.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}